{
    "quiz": {
      "title": "Easy Cinema and TV Shows Quiz",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the animated film about a clownfish searching for his son?",
          "options": ["Finding Dory", "Finding Nemo", "Toy Story", "Shrek"],
          "correct_answer": "Finding Nemo"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the protagonist in the 'Harry Potter' film series?",
          "options": ["Hermione Granger", "Ron Weasley", "Harry Potter", "Dumbledore"],
          "correct_answer": "Harry Potter"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which TV show features a group of friends living in New York City?",
          "options": ["The Simpsons", "Friends", "The Office", "How I Met Your Mother"],
          "correct_answer": "Friends"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the magical land in 'The Wizard of Oz'?",
          "options": ["Neverland", "Narnia", "Middle-earth", "Oz"],
          "correct_answer": "Oz"
        },
        {
          "question": "In 'The Lion King,' what type of animal is Simba?",
          "options": ["Elephant", "Lion", "Giraffe", "Monkey"],
          "correct_answer": "Lion"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the main character in the TV show 'SpongeBob SquarePants'?",
          "options": ["Patrick Star", "Squidward Tentacles", "SpongeBob SquarePants", "Sandy Cheeks"],
          "correct_answer": "SpongeBob SquarePants"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the superhero with a red cape and an 'S' on his chest?",
          "options": ["Spider-Man", "Superman", "Batman", "Iron Man"],
          "correct_answer": "Superman"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which animated film features a young mermaid named Ariel?",
          "options": ["Moana", "Frozen", "The Little Mermaid", "Brave"],
          "correct_answer": "The Little Mermaid"
        },
        {
          "question": "In 'Toy Story', what is the name of Woody's owner?",
          "options": ["Andy", "Tom", "Max", "Emily"],
          "correct_answer": "Andy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who played the character Jack Dawson in the film 'Titanic'?",
          "options": ["Brad Pitt", "Leonardo DiCaprio", "Tom Cruise", "Matthew McConaughey"],
          "correct_answer": "Leonardo DiCaprio"
        }
      ]
    }
  }
  